http://www.nsight-consulting.com/privacy.html

Privacy Policy
N-Sight Consulting respects the privacy of every individual who visits our websites. This Privacy Policy outlines the information N-Sight Consulting may collect and how we may use that information.Personal DataN-Sight Consulting will not collect any personally-identifiable information about you (e.g., your name, address, telephone number or email address ("personal data") through our websites unless you have provided it to us voluntarily. If you do not want your personal data collected, please do not submit it to us.When you do provide us with personal data, we may use that information in the following ways, unless stated otherwise: we may store and process that information to better understand your needs and how we can improve our products and services; we (or a fulfillment house or other third party on our behalf in connection with a promotion) may use that information to contact you; and/or we may provide other third parties with aggregate - but not individual - information about visitors to or users of our sites. We do not now and do not intend to sell, rent or market personal data about you to third parties.MinorsN-Sight Consulting has no intention of collecting any personal data from individuals under eighteen years of age, nor will this web site be promoted to minors.Adults should be aware that N-Sight's Privacy Policy will govern our use of personal data, but that information which is voluntarily given by anyone in chat sessions, email exchanges, bulletin boards or the like may be used to generate unsolicited mail. N-Sight encourages all adults to instruct minors in their care in the safe and responsible use of their personal data while using the Internet.Additional Information Collected AutomaticallyIn some cases, we may automatically (i.e., not via registration) collect technical information when you connect to our site that is not personally-identifiable. Examples of this type of information include the type of Internet Browser you are using, the type of computer operating system you are using and the domain name of the website from which you linked to our site.Information Placed Automatically on Your Computer - "Cookies"N-Sight Consulting has a policy of not storing information on your computer in the form of a "Cookie" or similar file. However, N-Sight's affiliates and partners may use these types of files in order to help them in many ways. For example, Cookies allow them to tailor linked websites to better match your interests and preferences. With most Internet Browsers, you can erase Cookies from your computer hard drive, block all Cookies or receive a warning before a Cookie is stored. Please refer to your Browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions.
N-Sight Consulting LLC331 Carpenter Drive NE, Suite 10Atlanta, GA 30328Phone: 404.847.9585   Toll-free: 844.9.NSIGHT (844.967.4448)   Fax: 941.847.9585Copyright 2019 - N-Sight Consulting LLC - All rights reserved
